buxfer.com 2009-05-14

# Buxfer: Free online personal finance software for budgeting and expense management. Track shared expenses, split bills, and debts. Transfer money online and settle IOUs with friends/roommates. Get alerts on your mobile device (iPhone, Blackberry and more) Track your money, Effortlessly!

Loading ...

Buxfer, Inc. ("Buxfer") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting the Buxfer’s website at http://www.buxfer.com (“buxfer.com”), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover? 

This Privacy Policy covers Buxfer’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Buxfer gathers when you are accessing buxfer.com and when you use our services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Buxfer does not own or control, or to individuals that Buxfer does not employ or manage. 

What Personal Information Does Buxfer display or Collect? 

The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our services, and to allow our users to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through buxfer.com. In connection with buxfer.com, we request and display some personal information to other users and visitors of buxfer.com, which allows users to identify each other. We collect the following types of information from our users. 

  * **Personal Information You Provide to Us**

We receive and store any information you enter on buxfer.com or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, age, gender, zip code, e-mail address, cell phone number, occupation, hometown, college, personal interests, nickname, and information about personal finances that is entered on buxfer.com. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to interact with other users, responding to your requests for certain information, products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features. 

  * **Personal Information Collected Automatically**
    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with buxfer.com or obtain services from us. Buxfer automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your browser type, IP address, Buxfer cookie information, and the page you requested. We also record the details of your transactions on buxfer.com. 
    * Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Buxfer only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of buxfer.com or services so that we can make buxfer.com appealing to as many users as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and buxfer.com, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, Buxfer never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 
  * **E-mail Communications**

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Buxfer if your computer supports this type of program. Buxfer uses this confirmation to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users. 

  * **Browser Cookies**
    * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Buxfer cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. 
    * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We require that cookies be enabled for you to take advantage of the services we offer on buxfer.com. 
    * Ads appearing on buxfer.com may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Buxfer and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Will Buxfer Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives? 

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below. 

  * _Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums_ : We provide publicly accessible areas on buxfer.com, and any information posted therein will be publicly available. 
  * _Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control_ : We link to other websites, controlled by other businesses. Linked businesses may sell services or items to you through buxfer.com. In other situations, Buxfer may provide services, or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share user information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. In particular, but without limitation, we link to the Amazon Payments system to allow users to process payments between one another. We will share user information to enable users to engage in transactions via Amazon Payments. 
  * _Agents_ : We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending email, analyzing data, and providing user services. Unless we tell you differently, Buxfer’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. 
  * _User profiles_ : User profile information including users’ name, phone number, email address, and information you enter about your personal finances (“User Submissions”) may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within buxfer.com. E-mail addresses are used to add new User Submissions to user profiles and to communicate through User Submissions. Users’ full names and email addressed will not be directly revealed to other users by Buxfer, except, when the user is "connected" to another user via a transaction, shared group membership, or an invitation. 
  * _Communication in response to User Submissions_ : As part of buxfer.com and Services, you will receive from Buxfer and other users ,e-mail and other communication relating to your User Submissions. You acknowledge and agree that by posting such User Submissions, Buxfer and other users may send you e-mail and other communication that they determine in their sole discretion relate to your User Submissions. 
  * _Promotional Offers_ : We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send us an email to unsubscribe. 
  * _Business Transfers_ : In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Buxfer, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Buxfer goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Buxfer may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 
  * _Protection of Buxfer and Others_ : We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Buxfer, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 
  * _With Your Consent_ : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information. 

Is Personal Information About me Secure? 

Your Buxfer account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need ensure unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

Buxfer endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Buxfer cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. For additional information about the security measures Buxfer uses in connection with buxfer.com, please contact us at support@bbleepuxfer.com. 

Buxfer.com contains links to other sites. Buxfer is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on buxfer.com. 

What Personal Information Can I Access? 

Buxfer allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as buxfer.com changes. You may currently access the following information: 

  * account information
  * user profile
  * user preferences
  * nickname
  * cell phone number

What Other Choices Do I Have? 

  * As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Buxfer features. 
  * You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 
  * You may request deletion of your Buxfer account by sending an e-mail to our webmaster at support@bbleepuxfer.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 
  * Buxfer may use a user’s e-mail address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding buxfer.com or Buxfer services. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the buxfer.com, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Buxfer may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you via e-mail or by posting an announcement on buxfer.com. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses buxfer.com after such changes have been first posted. 

Questions or Concerns 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at buxfer.com, please send us a detailed message to support@bbleepuxfer.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

_Adopted July 27, 2007._
